// Creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What CAN all living organisms do?",
    answer: "D. All the above",
    options: [
      "A. Use their senses to their environment",
      "B. Use energy to work",
      "C. Grow and change",
      "D. All the above",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Science is basically based on what?",
    answer: "C. Evidences",
    options: [
      "A. Beliefs",
      "B. Consensus",
      "C. Evidences",
      "D. Opinion",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "What is a theory?",
    answer: "B. A testable hypothesis or prediction that is potentially falsifiable",
    options: [
      "A. An experimental procedure of many observations, facts, and results",
      "B. A testable hypothesis or prediction that is potentially falsifiable",
      "C. A belief shared with many scientists agreeing on the topic",
      "D. An observation on something in the natural world",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is NOT a possibility of how life started?",
    answer: "B. Homeostasis",
    options: [
      "A. Extraterrestrial Origin",
      "B. Homeostasis",
      "C. Special Creation",
      "D. Spontaneous Origin",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following theory says that life-forms may have been put on Earth by supernatural divine forces?",
    answer: "C. Special Creation",
    options: [
      "A. Extraterrestrial Origin",
      "B. Homeostasis",
      "C. Special Creation",
      "D. Spontaneous Origin",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What did Charles Darwin state in the book 'On the Origin of the Species'?",
    answer: "B. Theory of Evolution",
    options: [
      "A. Extraterrestrial Origin",
      "B. Theory of Evolution",
      "C. Special Creation",
      "D. Theory of Panspermia",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which of the following theory is at the core of most major religions?",
    answer: "C. Special Creation",
    options: [
      "A. Extraterrestrial Origin",
      "B. Theory of Evolution",
      "C. Special Creation",
      "D. Theory of Panspermia",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following is defined as any process of formation or growth?",
    answer: "A. Evolution",
    options: [
      "A. Evolution",
      "B. Homeostasis",
      "C. Origin",
      "D. Process",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "There is NO exact date of how life started.",
    answer: "C. True",
    options: [
      "A. False",
      "B. Maybe",
      "C. True",
      "D. Undetermined",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Which of the following theory is a counterhypothesis to spontaneous generation?",
    answer: "A. Biogenesis Theory",
    options: [
      "A. Biogenesis Theory",
      "B. Evolution Theory",
      "C. Special Creation",
      "D. Theory of Panspermia",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What are general early forms of life?",
    answer: "B. microfossils",
    options: [
      "A. cyanobacteria",
      "B. microfossils",
      "C. microorganisms",
      "D. stromatolites",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What do you call the remnants of life embedded and trapped on the rocks?",
    answer: "B. microfossils",
    options: [
      "A. cyanobacteria",
      "B. microfossils",
      "C. microorganisms",
      "D. stromatolites",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "What do you call the cell structures that break down food to produce energy?",
    answer: "B. Mitochondria",
    options: [
      "A. Chloroplasts",
      "B. Mitochondria",
      "C. Ribosomes",
      "D. Vacuoles",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "Which of the following organelles works as the brain of the cell?",
    answer: "D. Nucleus",
    options: [
      "A. Lysosomes",
      "B. Mitochondria",
      "C. Nucleolus",
      "D. Nucleus",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which of the following organelles is NOT found in animal cells?",
    answer: "B. Cell wall",
    options: [
      "A. Cell membrane",
      "B. Cell wall",
      "C. Mitochondria",
      "D. Ribosomes",
    ],
  },
];
